# **Daniel Letch**

Bournemouth Dorset BH9 2UA

Home: 01202 514428 | Mobile: 07572 750401 | Email: danletch93@gmail.com | Github: ?| Linkedin: ????

## **PERSONAL PROFILE:**

I'm a 30 year old Junior Developer looking to grow and improve much more to become a skilled front end developer. I discovered the world of web development a few years ago and was hooked. I decided to carry out multiple online courses and delve through many hours of self study to get a good understanding and starting level to start off my new career.

### **SKILLS & ATTRIBUTES:**

- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- React
- Next JS
- Svelte
- SvelteKit
- SASS
- Tailwind
- Bootstrap
- GSAP
- Accessibility

- MJML Emails
- Wordpress
- Multiple CMS systems
- Customer service
- Communication
- Interpersonal
- Lone working
- Problem-solving
- Organisation
- Clean driving licence

## **EXPERIENCE:**

The majority of my time within my current company has been working as a content editor for our main client Visa. Alongside Visa I have also carried out content editing for Quintet bank and Waterside. I've also supported on but also built and tested promotions for Visa which was great as improved my coding and styling skills. The developers in the company have given me small tasks and training to help improve my skills especially within the last year. Recently I have been given the title of Junior Developer which was great to see my hard work rewarded.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:**

**Bright Blue Day,** Parkway House, Bournemouth, BH2 5SL (August 2022 to present)

**Mountain Warehouse**, Castlepoint Shopping Centre, Castle Lane West, Bournemouth, BH8 9UZ (December 2021 to August 2022)

Managed to become a supervisor quickly which has taught me the skills to teach and lead others along with keeping a team together happy.

Scott Castle Ltd, 743 Christchurch Road, Bournemouth, BH7 6AN (June 2017 to August 2021)

Helped to vastly improve my customer service skills and confidence.

**Bofa International Ltd**, 19-20 Creekmoor Industrial Estate, Balena Close, Creekmoor, Poole, BH17 7DU (January 2016 to June 2017)

Allowed me to work as a valued member of the team in a large company.

**Wessex Power Technology Ltd**, Wahn Fried, Winterbourne Zelston, DT11 9EX (July 2013 to October 2015)

Enabled me to complete my apprenticeship.

**Cathelco Seafresh Desalinators Ltd**, Unit 7, 11-15 Francis Avenue, Bournemouth (August 2011 to June 2013)

This was my first "real" job which I thoroughly enjoyed and let me to grow into a working environment.

#### **EDUCATION:**

Joined the Special Constabulary (September 2015)

Bournemouth and Poole College (September 2011 to July 2015)

Paragon Training Ltd, Ashley Road, Bournemouth (July 2010 to March 2011)

Winton Arts and Media College (September 2005 to June 2010)

## **QUALIFICATIONS:**

NVQ Level 3 in Electrical and Electronic Engineering NVQ Level 2 in Electrical and Electronic Engineering NVQ Level 2 in Engineering and Technology

## GCSE's:

English Language - C
Mathematics - C
Business Studies - C
History - C
French - C
Physical Education - C
Science - D

ICT (Information Communication Technology) - D

## **INTERESTS:**

I enjoy keeping fit and looking after my health and well-being by training at the gym regularly and going for runs and walks. I have a number of sports I like to play and train from time to time which includes badminton, martial arts, paddle boarding and golf. I enjoy relaxing with friends whether that be going to a bar for a drink or a trip out to a new place and I also enjoy fishing, watching films and playing computer games.